

Riccardo Martinello

Computer Science Student

Phone: +393315804865

Email: rickyma686@gmail.com

LinkedIn: /in/riccardo-martinello/

GitHub: /IsThisDemi

Website: riccardo.martinello.dev

I'm a computer science student based in Vicenza, Italy. I enjoy creating things that live on the internet, whether that be websites, applications, or anything in between. Skilled in Front-end Development. I have 5+ years of experience in HTML, CSS, C, C++, Bootstrap, Three.js. Hence, I have successfully completed several web projects from scratch. Yet, I learn continuously and never stop exploring new technologies.

Skills

I already know

HTML5 4/5 CSS 3/5 C 3/5 C++ 3/5 Bootstrap 4/5 Three.js 2/5

Tailwind CSS 2/5 PostgreSQL 3/5

I speak

Italian native English C1

Work experience

Senior front-end developer

February 2020 - now

Google

- In tristique vulputate augue vel egestas.
- Quisque ac imperdiet tortor, at lacinia ex.
- Duis vel ex hendrerit, commodo odio sed, aliquam enim.
- Ut arcu nulla, tincidunt eget arcu eget, molestie vulputate nisi.
- Nunc malesuada leo et est iaculis facilisis.
- Fusce eu urna ut magna malesuada fringilla.

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, Nx, Firebase

React.js developer

April 2019 - February 2020

Facebook

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process.

- Aenean eget ultricies felis. Pellentesque dictum massa ut tellus eleifend, sed posuere massa mattis.
- Ut posuere massa lacus, eleifend molestie tortor auctor vel.
- Sed sed sollicitudin eros, id ultricies mi. Aliquam sodales elit vel ante tempor, non vehicula nibh facilisis.
- Cras feugiat ultricies maximus. Aliquam tristique ex odio, ac semper urna accumsan a.

Technologies: React.js, React Query, Chakra UI, ESLint

Junior front-end developer

September 2016 - April 2019

GitLab

Nulla volutpat justo ante, rhoncus posuere massa egestas in:

- Quisque pellentesque, dolor nec sollicitudin iaculis, sem velit consequat ligula, eget tempus ligula leo et est.
- Maecenas ut elit sit amet nibh maximus condimentum in nec lorem. Pellentesque tincidunt odio vel leo suscipit, in interdum mi gravida.

Donec non vulputate augue 🌚

Technologies: Vue.js, Tailwind CSS, pnpm

Projects

Golden Bulls March 2020 - now

In tristique vulputate augue vel egestas. Quisque ac imperdiet tortor, at lacinia ex. Duis vel ex hendrerit, commodo odio sed, aliquam enim. Ut arcu nulla, tincidunt eget arcu eget, molestie vulputate nisi. Nunc malesuada leo et est iaculis facilisis.

Demo: https://golden-bulls-d73jd7.netlify.app

Repository: https://github.com/mark-freeman/golden-bulls

Technologies: Next.js, SASS, pnpm, ESLint, Prettier

TruQuest

June 2019 - February 2020

Ut ultricies tortor at sodales aliquam. Vivamus metus ante, fringilla nec ligula in, suscipit rhoncus mauris. Praesent hendrerit velit odio, at accumsan urna faucibus convallis. Nunc at massa eget ligula volutpat dictum a sit amet libero. Vestibulum iaculis molestie maximus. In hac habitasse platea dictumst.

Demo: https://tru-quest-ck7ea3.netlify.app

Repository: https://github.com/mark-freeman/tru-quest

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process.

Technologies: React.js, Tailwind CSS, NestJS, PostgreSQL

Software Chasers

January 2018 - December 2020

Quisque id consectetur eros. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Sed eu pulvinar orci. Mauris consequat, est in dignissim varius, neque nisl commodo mauris, id blandit risus justo eu nulla.

Demo: https://software-chasers-e82l8e.netlify.app

Repository: https://github.com/mark-freeman/software-chasers

Technologies: React.js, Chakra UI, TypeScript, Nx, pnpm

Disco Ninjas

May 2016 - July 2018

Praesent eu neque tortor. Vestibulum ac magna nisl. Vivamus massa sem, feugiat in pharetra non, convallis egestas purus. Ut consequat ullamcorper sem, in euismod nibh posuere ut.

Demo: https://disco-ninjas-g321ol.netlify.app

Repository: https://github.com/mark-freeman/disco-ninjas

Technologies: TypeScript, Jest, Firebase

Education

Bachelor's Degree

October 2020 - October 2024

University of Padova

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Science High School

September 2015 - July 2020

Liceo scientifico G.B.Quadri

High School Diploma. Specialization in applied sciences.